<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ubuntu on forevergenin</title>
    <link>https://www.forevergenin.com/tags/ubuntu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ubuntu on forevergenin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 14:17:48 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.forevergenin.com/tags/ubuntu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapping a debian rootfs for use with chroots/containers</title>
      <link>https://www.forevergenin.com/posts/linux/bootstrapping-debian-rootfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 14:17:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.forevergenin.com/posts/linux/bootstrapping-debian-rootfs/</guid>
      <description>The aim this time is to setup a base rootfs for Ubuntu/Debian distro which can be used for setting up a chroot jail or to create a docker container base image. This blog is based on a earlier blog which I have written but forgot to publish around June, 2012.
The below mentioned steps are validated on Fedora 25 Workstation installation.
For setting up a debian based rootfs we need a tool called debootstrap. It&amp;rsquo;s available as part of EPEL repository for Fedora and other Redhat based distros. Make sure to always install the latest version of debootstrap.
sudo dnf install debootstrap To setup a base rootfs you need to decide on the version of debian distro (wheezy, jessie, buster), the target architecture (i386 or amd64) and what kind of variant you want to setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forwarding DNS server on Ubuntu 16.04</title>
      <link>https://www.forevergenin.com/posts/networking/forwarding-dns-server-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 23:22:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.forevergenin.com/posts/networking/forwarding-dns-server-setup/</guid>
      <description>Goal We are looking to setup up a minimal forwarding DNS server on Ubuntu 16.04. After that we will see how to use nsupdate and dig to verify our configuration.
Prerequisites A VM running Ubuntu 16.04 with BIND installed You need root access for the VM External DNS server information We are going to use google&amp;rsquo;s DNS servers (8.8.8.8 and 8.8.4.4) as our external servers. In case a query can&amp;rsquo;t be resolved by our DNS server it will forward the request to the external server. Domain information We need to know the domain topology we want our DNS server to manage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
