<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manga on forevergenin</title>
    <link>http://www.forevergenin.com/categories/manga/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manga on forevergenin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@forevergenin.com (Premkumar Subramanian)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@forevergenin.com (Premkumar Subramanian)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2012 - 2017, Premkumar Subramanian; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 14:19:04 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.forevergenin.com/categories/manga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Manga Tracking List</title>
      <link>http://www.forevergenin.com/pages/my-manga-tracking-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 14:19:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <author>hello@forevergenin.com (Premkumar Subramanian)</author>
      <guid>http://www.forevergenin.com/pages/my-manga-tracking-list/</guid>
      <description>Last updated on August 26, 2017  “Every form of addiction is bad, no matter whether the narcotic be alcohol, morphine or idealism.” ― C.G. Jung
 This is my official track list for all the Mangas/Manhwas I have completed or currently reading.
Currently Reading:  One Piece 879 Tales of Demons and Gods 108 Gamble Fish 1 Noblesse 478 Spirit Blade Mountain 137 D.Gray-Man 225 Adventures of Sindbad - Prototype 138 Blood and Steel 71 Witch Hunter 169 Boruto: Naruto Next Generations 14 Berserk 352 Kingdom 533 Ao No Exorcist 94 Freezing 208 Tokyo Ghoul:re 142 Magi 351 Nanatsu no Taizai 236 Cavalier Of The Abyss 136 Knight Run 170 Nanatsu no Taizai: Seven Days 6 Hunter X Hunter 363 A Thousand Years Ninetails 86 Onepunch Man 128 Shingeki no Kyojin - Lost Girls 2 Freezing Zero 38 Dragon Ball Super27 The Gamer 192 The God of High School 328 Shingeki no Kyojin 98 King of Hell 332 Kubera 306 Golden Kamui 88 Vinland Saga 134 Attack On Titan - Before The Fall 11 Shingeki no Kyojin - Birth of Levi: Kuinaki Sentaku 10 City of Dead Sorcerer 138 Minamoto-kun Monogatari 195 Break Blade 86 Fairy Tail Blue Mistral Wendel&amp;rsquo;s Adventure 2 Tate no Yuusha no Nariagari 34 Tale of Eun Aran 83 Abide in the Wind 4 Fairy Tail Gaiden - Kengami no Souryuu 15 Tale of the Fighting Freak, Path of the Warrior - Blood and Steel 3 Ouroboros 102 Tales of the unusual 178 Baki - Son of Ogre 161 Kyoukai no Rinne 213 Urusei Yatsura 7 Magician 374 White Epic 96 Ruler of the land 527 Trinity Wonder 31 Black Haze 208 Black Clover 117 Desire Climax 7  Completed:  Lone Wolf and Cub Full Metal Alchemist Rurouni Kenshin Get Backers Rave Wolf Guy Ookami no Monshou 666 Satan Inuyasha Rosario-Vampire Record of Fallen Vampire The Breaker Kekkaishi Defense Devil Hellsing Dark Mage Arago Zero Flame of Recca Mahou Tsukai Kurohime Basilisk Magico Katekyo Hitman Reborn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naruto comes to an end</title>
      <link>http://www.forevergenin.com/posts/manga/naruto-comes-to-an-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 21:11:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <author>hello@forevergenin.com (Premkumar Subramanian)</author>
      <guid>http://www.forevergenin.com/posts/manga/naruto-comes-to-an-end/</guid>
      <description>Finally, after much deliberation I have decided to spend some time on maintaining a personal blog (more about this decision later). Now the question is what should be my first post? Much like most of the decisions I have made in my life I left this one as well to randomness and I stumbled upon this article at Kotaku.
Though it was my first manga, the truth is I was not worried much about the end.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>